Guide to the Gay and Lesbian Pulp Fiction Collection 1955-1988 MSS 116 MSS.116
Fales Library and Special Collections
- First Accretion
  - HIS '69. 69265. Bennett, P.H: Trade Secret. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - HIS '69. 69269. Gronowski, Paul: Rough-Ridin' Studs. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - HIS '69. 69272. West, Samuel: Backdoor Boy. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - HIS '69. 69274. Todd, Allen: Shafting Schoolboys. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - HIS '69. 69275. Hanley, Mark: Saddle Buddies. (Surree LTD.), 1979 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - HIS '69. 69401. Caldwell, Clay: Horny Studs' Ranch. (Surree LTD.), 1979 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - HIS '69. 69402. Bennett, PH: Trappin' Man II. (Surree LTD.), 1979 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - HIS '69. 69409. Gronowski, Paul: Bound For Pleasure. (Surree LTD.), 1980 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061142 1
  - HIS '69. 69410. Roberts, Todd: Behind the Man. (Surree LTD.), 1980 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - HIS '69. 69411. Riggles, John: Leather Sucker. (Surree LTD.), 1980 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - HIS '69. 69414. Gronowski, Paul: Pleasure Slave III. (Surree LTD.), 1980 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - HIS '69. 69415. Stroth, Dick: Growing Up Hard. (Surree LTD.), 1980 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - HIS '69. 69416. Todd, Allen: Junior Jocks. (Surree LTD.), 1980 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - HIS '69. 69417. Hartley, Jon: Pleasure Boy. (Surree LTD.), 1980 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - HIS '69. 69425. Sloan, Harold: Mountain Man. (Surree LTD.), 1981 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - HIS '69. 69426. Dante, Mark: Beware of the Greeks. (Surree LTD.), 1981 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - HIS '69. 69427. Graeme, Roland: The Captain's Mast. (Surree LTD.), 1981 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - HIS '69. 69429. Caldwell, Clay: Makin' The Team. (Surree LTD.), 1981 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - HIS '69. 69430. Todd, Allen: Willing Schoolboys. (Surree LTD.), 1981 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - HIS '69. 69432. Ward, Michael: Randy Pants. (Surree LTD.), 1981 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - HIS '69. 69433. Hartley, Jon: First Encounters. (Surree LTD.), 1981 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - HIS '69. 69434. West, Samuel: Fresh Meat. (Surey Books), 1981 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - HIS '69. 69435. Graeme, Roland: Lusty Lifeguards. (Surey Books), 1981 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - HIS '69. 69436. Benton, Josh: Jackin' Buddies. (Surey Books), 1981 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - HIS '69. 69438. Hartley, Jon: Slave Quarters. (Surey Books), 1981 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - HIS '69. 69464. Benton, Josh: Bath House Pick-Up. (Surey House), 1983 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Homosexual Classics. Anonymous: Tool Box. (s.l; [Fully Illustrated]), undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Homosexual Classics. Anonymous: Well Hung Hero. (s.l; [Fully Illustrated]), undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Impact Library 228. Carruthers, R.C.: Adam and Adam. (Echelon), 1967 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Impact Library 233. Trokki, A.L: Quatres of Cherry Grove. (Echelon Books), 1967 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Impact Library 234. Wade, Carlson: Naked In Sodom. (Echelon Books), 1967 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Impact Library 240. Crandell, Barry: Duet For Two. (Echelon Books), 1968 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Impact Library 241. Mosher, W.F.: Other Than A Man. (Echelon Books), 1968 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Impact Library 242.Trocci, H.L: Melody of Spring. (Echelon Books), 1968 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Impact Library 243. Crandall, Barry: Lavender Lads. (Echelon), 1968 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061143 9
  - Impact Library 328. Crandall, Barry: The Muscle Swappers. (Echelon), 1968 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Impact Library 332. McGraw, Rod: The Swinging Wind. (Echelon), 1968 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Impact Library 340. Harper, James: Another Room-Another Brother. (Echelon), 1968 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Imperial Books 735. Worthy, Ken: The Homosexual Generation. (L.S. Publications), 1965 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Jade Books 201. Bradley, Matt: Homo Hill. (Onsco Publications), 1963 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Just Us Guys 111. Schooter, J.W: Stud Swingtime. (American Art Enterprises), 1988 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Jove Books M4846. Nader, George: Chrome. (Jove Publications), 1978 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Kozy Book 167. Bowie, Joe D: Half World. (Kozy Book Inc.), 1962 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Kozy Book 184. Anonymous: Male Bride. (Kozy Book Inc.), 1963 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Kozy Book 191. Anonymous: When Men Meet. (Kozy Book Inc.), 1963 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Lancer Books 73-578. Rico, Don: The Man From Pansy. (Lancer), 1967 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Lancer Books 73-639. Rico, Don: The Daisy Dilemma. (Lancer), 1967 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Lambda Press 102. Forbes, Jason: The Happy Hustler. (Lambda Press), 1974 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Lambda Press 105. Saison, Jacques: The Man's Man. (Lambda Press), 1968 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Lambda Press 108. Allyson, Kim: His Male Lover. (Lambda Press), 1970 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Lambda Press 109. Maggie, John: Honey Boy. (Lambda Press), 1969 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Lambda Press 110. Tempus, Brad: The Gay Brotherhood. (Lambda Press), 1974 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Late-Hour Library 734. Mark, Julian: Little Boy Lavender. (Phenix Publishers), 1967 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Late-Hour Library 735. Davidson, Chris: The Last Cruise. (Phenix Publishers), 1967 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Late-Hour Library 760. Dodd, Sam: Donnie and Clyde. (Phenix Publishers), 1968 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Late-Hour Library 763. Holliday, Don: Blow The Man Down. (Phenix Publishers), 1968 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Late-Hour Library 768. Dale, Dick: The Price of Pansies. (Phenix Publishers), 1968 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Late-Hour Library 771. Lester, Lance: Lights Out, Little Hustler. (Phenix Publishers), 1968 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Late-Hour Library 772. Davidson, Chris: The Gay Gods. (Phenix Publishers), 1968 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Late-Hour Library 775. Dale, Dick: Mr. Fancy-Pants. (Phenix Publishers), 1968 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Lavender Publications 25. Greene, Aron: Sin Sucker. (s.l), undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061144 7
  - Leisure Book 1172. Williams, J.X.: The Bronze and the Wine. (Corinth), 1966 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Leisure Book 1177. Holliday, Don: The Sun Goes Down. (Corinth), 1966 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Leisure Book 1184. Holliday, Don: Gothic Gaye. (Corinth), 1966 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Leisure Book 1212. Miller, Marcus: Locker-Room Lovers. (Corinth), 1967 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - LeSalon's Thunderbolt Books. Anonymous: School Stud. (s.l), undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Lesbian Diary. Treat: Jackie. (s.l), undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Lion Library Edition 128. Garland, Rodney: The Troubled Midnight. (Olympia Publications), 1954 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Little Library Press 3001. Kermeen, Conner: Little Boy Blew. (Little Library Press), 1971 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Little Library Press 3003. Wood, Edw. D, Jr.: To Make a Homo. (Corinth), 1971 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Locker Room Library 101. Tulane, Rick: His Brother's Keeper. (Publisher's Consultants), 1977 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Locker Room Library 105. Patcher, E.E.: Yesterday's Trade. (Publisher's Consultants), 1977 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Locker Room Library 106. Blake, Vic: Getting The Shaft. (Publisher's Consultants), 1977 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Locker Room Library 107. Temple, Dal: Pacific Phallusades. (Publisher's Consultants), 1977 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - MacFadden Books 75-173. Miller, H.D: I Love Thee, Beast. (MacFadden), 1966 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Male-Oriented 100. Anonymous: His Abnormal Love. (s.l), undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Male-Oriented 200. Anonymous: That Gay Bar. (s.l), undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Manhard Series 402. Love, D.H: DIAL-A-DICK. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Manhard Series 403. Kincaid, Jeff: Officer Dick. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Manhard Series 404. Cummings, Rich: Pay As You Come. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Manhard Series 405. Kincaid, Jeff: The Reamer. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Manhard Series 406. Martin, Jack: Put It In. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Manhard Series 407. Coxe, Jed: Ride A Hard Cop. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Manhard Series 410. Smith, Art: Two-Holer. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Manhard Series 411. Howard, Frank: Rim Rider. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Manhard Series 412. Rogers, Tom: Easy To Be Hard. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061145 4
  - Manhard Series 413. Marx, Richard: Cockwork Orange. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Manhard Series 414. Wynters, Bob: Long Hard Wynters. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Manhard Series 416. Glanz, Dick: By The Balls. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Manhard Series 417. Smith, Art: Mr. Suck. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Manhard Series 418. Coxe, Jed: Hot Load Trucker. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Manhard Series 419. Cochran, Bob: Snow-Job. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Manhard Series 420. Wynters, Bob: Wynter's Tail. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Manhard Series 422. Cummings, Rich: Buddy's Butt. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Manhard Series 423. Smith, Art: All Day Sucker. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Manhard Series 424. Todd, Eric: Beachballer. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Manhard Series 425. Cummings, Rich: Cock Fighters. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Manhard Series 426. Fletcher, O.J: Bunghole Buddies. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Manhard Series 430. Kincaid, Jeff: Brown-Sucker. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Manhard Series 431. Wynters, Bob: Wynter's Balls. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Manhard Series 432. Griffon, David: Ask Ol' Buddy. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Manhard Series 434. Smith, Art: Bunkhouse Boy. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Manhard Series 435. Rogers, Tom: Come Free. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Manhard Series 436. Love, D.H.: Blow The Joint. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Manhard Series 439. Coxe, Jed: Peter's Pink. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Manhard Series 440. Pepper, Peter: Meat Slinger. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Manhard Series 441. Martin, Damon: Long Hard Buck. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Manhard Series 444. Patterson, Art: Butt Rustle. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Manhard Series 445. Todd, Eric: Beachballer II. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Manhard Series 446. Rose, Dustin: Fist of Fire. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Manhard Series 447. Kincaid, Jeff: Water Sport. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061146 2
  - Manhard Series 449. Martin, Damon: Butt Bucker. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Manhard Series 451. Alpert, Jay: Put It In. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Manhard Series 453. Ray, Lowell: Brown Eye Boy. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Manhard Series 454. Garbo, Edward: Double Truckin'. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Manhard Series 455. Lynn, Steve: Peter Easter. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Manhard Series 456. Martin, Damon: Cocke Balls. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Manhard Series 457. Todd, Eric: Beachballer III. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Manhard Series 458. Michael, Jay: Do It Up Brown. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Manhard Series 460. Wilson, George: Throat Thriller. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Manhard Series 461. Savoy, Sam: Hot and Hard. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Manhard Series 462. Pines, Philips: Hard On His Tail. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Manhard Series 463. West, Samuel: Boy Meat. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Manhard Series 466. Roberts, Thomas: Chicken Lickin' Good. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Manhard Series 469. Gifford, Lon: Hard-On The Saddle. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Manhard Series 471. Richter, Art: Sucker For Seafood. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Manhard Series 473. Duncan, James: Pickin' The Chicken. (Surrey House), 1975 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Manhard Series 474. Johnson, Thumper: Rim Sheet. (Surrey House), 1975 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Manhard Series 476. Jennings, Newt: Bondage and Boyflesh. (Surrey House), 1975 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Manhard Series 479. Pines, Philip: The Sergeant's Privates. (Surrey House), 1975 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Manhard Series 480. West, Samuel: Deliveries In The Rear. (Surrey House), 1975 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Manhard Series 486. Gronowski, Paul: Double Play. (Surrey House), 1978 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Manhard Series 494. Lamb, Sebastian: Man Slave. (Surrey House), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Manhard Series 495. Michaels, Bob: Inside Man. (Surrey House), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Manor Books 12260. Rule, Jane: Against The Season. [Signature Copy]. (Manor Books), 1975 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Manor Books 19112. Porter, Darwin: Butterflies in Heat. (Manor Books), 1976 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Midwood 32-550. Emerson, Jill: Enough of Sorrow. [Winner of the 1965 Midwood Award for Literary Excellence]. (Tower Publications) (Box 24, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061147 0
  - Midwood 35-149. Greene, Jay: Pretty Boy. (Midwood Publications), 1968 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Midwood 35-192. Greene, Jay: Bitter Wine. (Midwood Enterprises), 1969 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Midwood 35-204. Greene, Jay: Nino. (Midwood Enterprises), 1969 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Midwood 35-225. James, Sky: Bunk Buddies. (Midwood Enterprises), 1969 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Midwood 35-239. Hamilton, Greg: Strange Worlds; Harmon, Lee: Strange Roommates. (Midwood Enterprises), 1969 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Midwood 508. 60696. Scott, Michael: Private Passions. (Midwood), 1976 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Midwood 508. 60715. Scott, Michael: Gay Psycho. (Midwood Publications), 1976 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Midwood 508M-175-21. Roberto: Satyricon 70.. (Midwood Enterprises), 1970 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Midwood 508M-195-10. Greene, Jay: Cruising. (Midwood Enterprises), 1970 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Midwood 508M-195-38. Kovar, Dallas: Blow Gently. (Midwood Enterprises), 1971 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Nightstand Book 1857. Holliday, Don: Gay Buddies. (Corinth Publications), 1967 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Nightstand Book 1859. Miller, Marcus: A Masculine Scent. (Corinth), 1967 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Nightstand Book 1880. Miller, Marcus: Boy Meets Boy. (Corinth), 1968 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Nite Time Original 123. Jacobs, Edward: Gay Boy. (Golden State News), undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Numbers Illustrated Library 115. Moore, Martin: To Dare To Be Different. (Blue boy Library), 1978 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Numbers Paperback Library 10005. Wilson, George: Whipping Cream. (Numbers), 1978 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Numbers Paperback Library 10015. Hoban, Steve: Men of the Blue Grass. (Numbers), 1978 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Olympia Press 26. Hurch, Charles: The Feel-It Book. (Olympia Press), 1971 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Ophelia Press 106. Van Heller, Marcus: Jailbirds In The Backseat. (Ophelia), undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Oracle Books 88-606. Squire, Eugene: Cross-Country Trick. (Oracle Books), 1969 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Pad Library 522. Dickson, Paul: Gay Boy Returns. (Pad Library), 1966 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Paperback Library 54-821. Rand, Lou: Rough Trade. (Paperback Library), 1965 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Paperback Library 54-906. Deutsch, Deborah: The Flaming Heart. (Paperback Library), 1966 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Paper Jacks 0-7701-0068-6. Zaremba, Eve: A Reason To Kill. (Paper Jacks), 1978 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061148 8
  - Parisian Press 200. Laurie, Paul: Night Of The Sadist. (Parisian Press), 1971 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Parisian Press 201. Carey, Mike: Pool Boy. (Parisian Press), 1971 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Parisian Press 204. Sawyers, Rod: Gay Blades. (Parisian Press), 1971 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Parisian Press 205. Wilder, David: Fathers, Sons, and Lovers. (Parisian Press), 1971 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Parisian Press 206. Laurie, Paul: Come Killer, Come. (Parisian Press), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Parisian Press 207. Crane, Larry: My Dark Lover. (Parisian Press), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Parisian Press 216. Wilhelm, Lambert: Dog Collar Boys. (Parisian Press), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Parisian Press 220. Jackson, John: Intensive Care. (Parisian Press), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Parisian Press 222. Doyle, Patrick: All-American Stud. (Parisian Press), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Parisian Press 223. Lawrence, David: Lusty Seamen. (Parisian Press), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Parisian Press 225. Loring, Joseph: Teen-Aged Hustler. (Parisian Press), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Parisian Press 226. Rinker, David: City Boy. (Parisian Press), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Parisian Press 227. Jackson, John: Deadly Orgasm. (Parisian Press), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Parisian Press 229. Mario: Orgy Italian Style. (Parisian Press), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Parisian Press 230. Wilhelm, Lambert: Too Beautiful. (Parisian Press), undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Parisian Press 231. Prodde, Lance: Caribbean Sex. (Parisian Press), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Parisian Press 232. Jackson, John: It's Show Biz. (Parisian Press), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Parisian Press 233. Stevens, Eric: Military Orgy. (Parisian Press), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Parisian Press 234. Colby, Jim: Truckers' Delight. (Parisian Press), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Parisian Press 235. Esse, Jay: Wild From The Farm. (Parisian Press), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Parisian Press 236. MacMurphy, J.P: Room 314.. (Parisian Press), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Parisian Press 237. Farout, Billy: Hero In the Bedroom. (Parisian Press), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Parisian Press 238. Doyle, Patrick: Red. (Parisian Press), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Parisian Press 239. Malory, Stafford: The Boy Who Asked For More. (Parisian Press), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Parisian Press 240. COOP: Sexy Southern Boy. (Parisian Press), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Parisian Press 241. Fredericks, Carl: The Traveling Sex Man. (Parisian), 1972 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061149 6
  - Parisian Press 242. Parkhurst, Peter: Some Like It Hard. (Parisian Press), 1972 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Parisian Press 243. Lambert, Williams J.: Male Sex Idol. (Parisian Press), 1972 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - PEC Novel N121. Culver, Ed: Gay Three-Way. (Publishers' Export Co.), 1966 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Pendulum 0-421. Stark, Ben: Size Queen. (Pendulum), 1970 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Pleasure Reader 217. Davidson, Chris: Song of Alexander. (Phenix Publishers), 1969 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Pleasure Reader 218. Miller, Marcus: Gay Revolution. (Phenix), 1969 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Pleasure Reader 219. Thomas, Aaron: Deep Lavender. (Phenix), 1969 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Pleasure Reader 222. Lamarr, Barry: For The Love of Lavender. (Phenix), 1969 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Pleasure Reader 224. Porter, Dan: Ship Of Queens. (Phenix), 1969 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Pleasure Reader 225. Forbes, Jason: Made In England. (Phenix), 1970 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Pleasure Reader 274. Barker, Sonny: Shafter. (Phenix), 1970 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Pleasure Reader 275. Townsend, Larry: Two Thousand Sixty Nine Plus One. (Phenix), 1970 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Pleasure Reader 279. Scharde, Bernard: Happy-Go-Lightly. (Phenix), 1970 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Pleasure Reader 286. Frey, Gerrold: Ronnie. (Phenix Publishers), 1970 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Pleasure Reader 291. Forbes, Jason: Get It Up. (Phenix Publishers), 1970 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Pleasure Reader 298. Lansing, Shane: Hard, Hot Hard-Hat. (Greenleaf), 1971 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Pleasure Reader 299. Robinson, Bradbury: Bare Knees, Boy Knees. (Greenleaf), 1971 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Pleasure Reader 300. Hollingsworthy, Llewellyn: Brothers and Lovers. (Greenleaf), 1971 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Pleasure Reader 301. Thomas, Aaron: Sixty-Nine Palms. (Greenleaf), 1971 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Pleasure Reader 305. Dean, Douglas: Sidewalk Salesman. (Greenleaf), 1971 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Pleasure Reader 309. Falkon, Felix Lance: Nine Easy Pieces. (Greenleaf), 1971 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Pleasure Reader 310. Lambert, William J: Demon's Coronation. (Greenleaf), 1971 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Pleasure Reader 311. Hughes, Peter Tuesday: A Walk In The Park. (Greenleaf), 1971 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Pleasure Reader 318. Wayne, W.W.: Park Duty. (Greenleaf), 1971 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Pleasure Reader 317. Insley, James: Yours To Keep. (Greenleaf), 1971 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Pleasure Reader 319. Lambert, William J: Bob, Carl, Ted and Alan. (Greenleaf), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061150 4
  - Pleasure Reader 320. Sawyers, Rod: Fly Boys. (Greenleaf), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Pleasure Reader 323. Delacourt, George: Frontier Boys. (Greenleaf), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Pleasure Reader 326. Lester, Lance: MacNeil's Raiders. (Greenleaf), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Pleasure Reader 324. Hughes, Peter Tuesday: Graffiti. (Greenleaf), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Pleasure Reader 327. Dean, Douglas: Windows and Mirrors, Volume I. (Greenleaf), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Pleasure Reader 328. Dean, Douglas: Windows and Mirrors, Volume II. (Greenleaf), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Pleasure Reader 333. Dean, Douglas: A Father In the Shadows. (Greenleaf), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Pleasure Reader 336. Lester, Lance: Clint Scores Big. (Greenleaf), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Pleasure Reader 339. Raborg, Frederick: Gin Street Rhythms. (Greenleaf), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Pleasure Reader 350. Stuart, Chad: Blackballed. (Greenleaf), 1972 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Pleasure Reader 351. Delacourt, George: The Cabin Cruiser. (Greenleaf), 1972 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Pleasure Reader 357. Raborg, Frederick: Gay Vigilante. (Greenleaf), 1972 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Pleasure Reader 364. Daniels, Gordon: Black Angel. (Greenleaf), 1972 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Pleasure Reader 370. Stuart, Chad: Mountain Men. (Greenleaf), 1972 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Pleasure Reader 386. Andros, Phil: Renegade Hustler. (Greenleaf), 1972 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Pocket Books, 75103. Hays, H.R: The Dangerous Sex, The Myth of Feminine Evil. (Pocket Cardinal), 1965 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Pocket Books, 82317-5. Hunt, Morton: Gay. (Pocket Books), 1977 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Private Editions Novel 355. Wright, L.B: Queer Street. (Private Editions), 1965 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Private Editions Novel 375. Bright, Lynwood: The Men Between. (Private Editions), 1966 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Proctor File Illustrated 1006. Smith, Robert: Gay Mystique-How Men Love Men. (s.l.), undated (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Proctor File Illustrated 1007. Nitzer, Rodney: Gay Lovers-Hard Men With Hard Bodies. (s.l.), undated (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Proctor File Illustrated 1010. Proctor, Dr: Gay Rape-Forced Sexual Acts. (s.l.), undated (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Pyramid Books F-691. Fletcher, Flora: Whisper of Love. (Pyramid Books), 1955 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Pyramid Books G-278. Taylor, Dyson: Bitter Love. (Pyramid Books), 1957 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Pyramid Books X-262. Tellier, Andre: Twilight Men. (Pyramid Books), 1957 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - RAM-10. #103. Shalanski, Tex: Saddle Buddy. (Hamilton House), 1974 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061151 2
  - RAM-10. #104. Baldwin, Dick: Hunk. (Hamilton House), 1974 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - RAM-10. #105. Bronson, Wolfe: Truck Stop. (Hamilton House), 1974 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - RAM-10. #107. Kelly, Mike: The Big Pipe. (Hamilton House), 1974 (Box 28, Folder 4)